# **Ashley Park**

Raeford, NC

(919) 738-4850 | Mark Apark 8496@gmail.com | Image Apark 8496



### **Objective**

Front-end web developer leveraging background in English and linguistics to build an intuitive, user-friendly web experience. Certificate in Full Stack Web Development from the University of North Carolina at Charlotte, with newly developed skills in HTML, CSS, JS, React.js, as well as multiple backend technologies Excited to approach new and challenging tasks and leverage my skills as part of a face-paced, driven team to build better web experiences for users.



## **Experience**

Barista | Starbucks

OCT 2021 - CURRENT

Held various customer service roles including barista, sales assistant, and cashier in an extremely
fast-paced environment while working efficiently on a team to properly communicate to properly
provide quality, quick coffee, and uplifting service to customers.

Server | Umami JAN 2021 – SEP 2021

As a top server, played an instrumental role in improving and designing the menu's layout, and decrease
unpopular items to help maximize efficiency, save resources, reduce fees, and ensure the continuation and
enhancements of quality service.

#### Receptionist | Carolina Psychiatry

Nov 2019 – May 2020

Increased the proficiency of daily office operation and time management by 30% through helping initiate
multi-tasking duties and scheduling out specific task for each front-office employee, such as managing office
communication support between clients and Psychiatrist. As well as, through developing a system between
employees to optimize client record-keeping that eliminated a severe record-keeping accumulation within six
weeks of initial hiring.



#### **Education**

Certificate, Full-Stack Web Development | *University of North Carolina at Charlotte* Oct 2021 - Apr 2022

Bachelor's degree, English Language and Literature, General | *University of North Carolina at Pembroke* August 2016-December 2018



#### **Technical Skills**

Programing Languages	HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript	
Libraries/Frameworks	React.js, Express.js, Node.js, Git, Bootstrap, jQuery,	
Databases	MongoDB, MySQL	
Platforms	Heroku	